The world's angriest country is likely not the one you think it is, but honestly, the
way that these polls of the happiest or angriest countries are measured in the first place
is always slightly questionable to me.
So our plan is to investigate what's really happening in this country and why it's been
called the angriest.
To do so, we devised a challenge for ourselves to go deep with the locals.
We're not booking a hotel.
We'll be flying in, landing in the afternoon, and having just a few hours before dark to
make some friends and hopefully find a place to stay for the night.
Ammar, Staffan, and myself will be dropped off in three different neighborhoods with
three different cultural and religious backgrounds, hoping to get housed and get an experience
with some of the locals we encounter.
The only rule is they can't recognize us from YouTube.
So yes, you heard that correctly.
We're flying to the angriest country in the world, hoping to find a stranger to house  us.
But here's the question.
Why?
Well, the hotel room experience doesn't always guarantee you a connection with those who live there.
It shelters you from the realities and leave you distanced from the people.
And so, as we are seeking to find depth, hopefully meet people from all walks of life, and leave
room for some adventure, we decided to do this differently.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Yes Theory discovery of the country of Lebanon.
Well, how are you feeling, Ammar?
It's been like a childhood dream, it's like a neighboring country.
It's the first place in my mind that was like outside of Egypt that I like visualized visiting
or going to.
So it's pretty surreal to be back here.
Should be enough for the taxi.
Yeah.
Wow.
He was just the guy sitting next to us on the plane.
He was just like, yeah, here's access so that you don't get ripped off.
He gave you a bunch of cash.
It's hundreds of thousands.
Ammar posted in his story that we're flying to Beirut.
It wasn't that hard to track on which flight we'd be on.
We've got some Yes Fam members coming up, celebrating eight years of seeking discomfort.
Wow.
Nice shirt.
Thank you.
Let's go.
This is crazy.
That is sick.
As we celebrate eight years of Yes Theory today and Seekers Day, our biggest giveaway
day of the year on Seek Discomfort, getting surprised by the YesFam felt special.
And this year, we're really going all out.
On top of making Seek Discomfort clothing more accessible by taking 30% off our all-time
bestsellers, we have tons of surprises for those who participate.
You'll enter a raffle to win an all-expenses paid trip to LA with three of your friends.
You'll get access to the first chapter of Matt's Yes Theory book and a lot more.
Seek Discomfort is truly a big, big part of how we run this channel.
Your support keeps these videos alive and gives you a visual reminder to keep seeking
discomfort as a priority in your life for growth, connection, and adventure.
Seek Discomfort has never been more affordable than this week, so if you've ever considered
getting some, now would be the best time to do so.
You guys need a ride?
Yeah, we do.
We got you.
Okay, good.
So the goal is to stay with three strangers, three different stories.
I just cleaned my room this morning.
Unfortunately, you don't qualify.
We're gonna go exchange some money, get some SIM cards, and then start, get started.
It is hot.
All right.
This is how hot it is, if you're wondering.
What neighborhood am I getting dropped off in?
Hamra.
It's basically a student, student area.
Two of the biggest universities in Lebanon.
Oh, great. Students are good.
They'll be kind, but they might not have space to house me, so.
All the Arab artists and singers of the world spoke about Hamra and how beautiful it is.
All right.
So unfortunately, after the socioeconomic situation, after the explosion, it's become
a very poor neighborhood.
It's still beautiful and we still love it for what it is.
Because of the financial burdens that Lebanon had, because of its politicians.
Trying to build back up right now, but it's gonna take a while.
We're very positive people.
We have a happy spirit and we're all like, just pushing through, trying to make it.
Everyday, like it's our last.
Wow.
All right. So we're going to the main street in Hamra.
There are about 10 people exchanging money, and we're gonna see who has the best rate
and go with that rate.
Unfortunately, like a black market exchange, but it's what everybody does.
- 1.010? Euro?
- 1.10.
A country's currency collapsing is never the cause of one single decision.
But one of a series of events and neglect that happens over many, many years.
Lebanon has become, for all intents and purposes, a failed state.
Put simply, Lebanon has been grappling with decades of political instability and corruption.
After coming out of a civil war from 1975 to 1990, government mismanagement of the economy,
excessive borrowing and a lack of financial reforms,
led to a severe fiscal deficit and unsustainable debt levels.
As the situation worsened over the years,
this eventually flared up to wide-scale protests in 2019.
And when COVID hit, followed by the gigantic explosion in 2020
that caused billions of dollars of damage happened,
inflation went through the roof and the $1 that was once worth 1,500 Lebanese Lira
is now worth 91,000.
Making the Lebanese Lira about 60 times less valuable.
This used to be a lifetime worth of money for one family.
A lifetime. For like five, six people.
Okay, so we just exchanged 150 euros, which used to be how much?
$10,000. Now it's $150.
So how do people get by?
People that are still getting their salaries in Lebanese pounds
basically are below the poverty line.
It's a big issue here in Lebanon.
Are we starting?
Can we keep this group feeling for some more?
Staffan, you're really afraid of being let go.
Staffan does not want to be...
But it just feels nice to be in this group here.
This is your first time. You've never done an 'abandoned in' even.
I've never been in this part of the world before, but I love it.
It's the best place to start.
I will see you in 24 to 48 hours. Who knows?
I don't know where you guys are going, but I'm going here.
So I'm going to the beach.
What?
Good luck!
And the 24 hours begin.
Damn. So I'm here by myself.
I'm alone now.
Okay, guys. Change of plans.
Take me to the best shawarma place.
Okay.
I notice when I'm nervous, I start to act very weird.
Turn the mental blocks into building blocks and build up.
Okay.
Not many people here right now, but I'll find someone.
I feel like around when the sun's about to set,
that's when everyone comes out of hiding.
Okay. So I have about three hours until then.
I'll find someone before then, though.
- Hi, guys.
-  Hello.
We are on a mission that I'm going to try to find someone that can host me for the night.
If I wasn't having a party, I would say, we're open-door policy,
but I don't think you'd want to stay at our place tonight.
- Take care
- Thanks for the energy.
Well, I just met somebody who told me what I'm doing is not safe.
It's always fun and encouraging to hear.
- Do you speak English?
- Yeah, I do.
- I'm Thomas. Nice to meet you.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
So I'm here traveling in Lebanon,
Trying to get like, deep, imersed in the culture.
So I haven't booked a hotel.
- The thing is, I live in a dorm, so it's just one bed.
- Okay.
So it's not going to fit. I'm sorry.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. See you.
Damn, he was perfect.
I wonder what Ammar and Staffan are doing.
- Do you guys speak English?
- Yep.
Basically, there's three of us.
So each of our challenge is,
in each of our neighborhoods,
is to find a strange to house us
I might have a master plan here.
If I buy some flowers, I can give people flowers,
and that can be a great conversation starter.
- Hello. Are you from Beirut?
-  Yes.
You came today?
-  I came today, yeah. Two hours ago.
And now I'm going to try to find a home to sleep at tonight.
- Oh my God.
- hahaha, yes.
Can I maybe stay in your house tonight?
- We don't have place.
- Okay.  Okay.
I say shukran for I got good energy,
("Shukran" = "Thank you" in Arabic)
I got positivity, and I get flower here.  So I'm happy meeting you.
This one here?
- Four of these.
- Yes, thank you.  Shukran.
How much is this?
- Gift.
- Gift?
Let me pay you, Nadia.
No, never mind.
- You sure?
- Don't worry, yeah.
Thank you.  Okay, shukran.
You're welcome.
I've taken my sweet time to get started with this.
It said online that Lebanese people are the angriest worldwide.
On the contrary, you will see a good vibe.
We faced many crises.
However, we as the people of Lebanon,
We love life so much, we love nightlife.
Even the poor of us.
We have a popular saying:
"He borrows money in order to show himself in the best form,
he borrows money from his friends to decorate himself,
and he will pay off the debts later".
My challenge is to find someone from Beirut
who will be my host for the day.
I wish I could take you with me
but we are a huge family of 7 members.
Don't worry, I understand.
You are always welcome.
Thank you.
I would clear the house for you and you are welcome.
Thank you my friend.
You have a lovely smile and character.
I wish you luck and hope your video turns out great.
I hope so.
I swear, I've never had that many positive interactions back to back.
His family has seven members and he literally offered to host me tonight.
So, they love life and they don't let anything get in the way of that,
which is very inspiring.
This is called the Martyr Square.
Behind me, this is a mosque and a church right next to each other.
And this is apparently where the revolution in 2019 took place.
You can see the raised fist right there.
I have four flowers and one to each.
Oh, thank you!
- Thank you.
The wind goes this way.
Taxi? Okay I go with you.
Yeah, where do you want to go?
Hmm, a little adventure.
- I'm going to Hamra
- okay I go a little bit with you.
Hello! Yeah, Hi! Nice to meet you. I'm Staffan.
- Come sit here beside me
- Can I?
- Yeah, yalla
-Okay, Jalla. I come.
-No Problem
- Okay. Thank you Edna.
- Edna are we running a business together you and me now
- Yeah.
We want to welcome in. Welcome in. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you
- I love Lebanon.
- He is from Syria
- Are you from Syria? I love Syria. I love Syria
As I'm on my way to get dropped off, we're just passing by the Beirut port and seeing the aftermath of the explosion.
It breaks my heart and the boys are telling me like the buildings behind here were just all destroyed and they had to renovate everything.
The Beirut blast was one of the largest non-nuclear explosions in history.
For a country that was already seriously struggling the blast led to the displacement of 300,000 people from
their homes, neighborhoods destroyed, and ended the lives of 220 people.
This event was like a final blow leaving a massive visual scar in the heart of
the city in many ways echoing back and magnifying the challenges that this
country has been facing. What do you love the most with the Beirut? Everything.
It was beautiful. Now it's a little bit different. The explosion changed. It was awful really. We're still alive.
I can feel that and a lot of energy it feels like. On a lot of lists on the
internet they say Lebanon now is the angriest country. What the population is
suffering from isn't fair from the corruption and everything so it's their
right to be angry I feel. And I hope when I finish my education outside of Lebanon
I'd come back and like raise my children and get married here. Yeah me too. Because it's
such a nice country and it's perfect like nothing nothing's actually wrong
with it other than the economic crisis and the government.
What gives you hope now in your life here in Lebanon?
It's love. Love for the country. And you want to believe that it's gonna work out even if
the signs don't show. But we have faith and it's also no faith in the people you
know. Everyone wants the country to be better. I've had two civil wars.
We've had lots of conflict. I think people are just tired of fighting each
other and we just want something to fight for essentially.
And although we'd all clearly approached this challenge completely differently, none of us had yet
found a home and sunset was rapidly approaching. We'd have to find someone
now in the dark and the chances of us sleeping outside were seriously increasing.
I'm switching neighborhoods. It's not working out. I'm going to a more lively nightlife place.
You're from Beirut? Yeah I'm from Beirut.
I didn't book a hotel so I'm trying to stay with a local tonight. So I'm looking for people on the street that can help me.
Oh okay. Yeah yeah yeah.
Where are you from? I'm from Sweden. Sweden? Welcome.
Where are you from? Lebanon. Nice to meet you. Hi.
The old bread of Lebanese people. It's so good.
Well one reflection after being in Lebanon a full day is that people are so generous.
I just had some food. They refused to let me pay. Even like Adnan when I was in the cab.
He didn't want me to pay. I did pay him but like he didn't want me to pay.
And also the woman with the flowers. She didn't want me to pay.
People are just so generous giving, helping, caring.
And I often find that sometimes people who have the least they give the most.
But I have to say that I'm starting to become really tired.
Soon 10pm. Sh** I'm tired. It's been so many hours.
Okay so another change of plan. This is like the third neighborhood that I switched to.
These guys just told me that there's like a YesFam live gig happening in there.
Even though I'm on a mission to find a place to stay tonight I'm going to go and say hi and check it out.
Well worst case scenario I have a place you can stay over.
But I can't do that. It has to be a complete straight.
I was betting my life on you crashing.
We interrupt this program for a quick message from our sponsor.
Hello mates. Sorry to interrupt but did you know Seeker's Day is live?
Did you know it's 30% off site wide?
We've got bestsellers at all time and revamped styles.
To celebrate our 4th edition of Seeker's Day we're offering 4 exclusive bonuses if anybody buys this week.
Plus unlock a free chapter of Matt's book!
Also get exclusive access to 1 hour live Q&A with Thomas and Ammar.
And there's a free mystery gift.
There's a chance to win a paid trip to LA to visit the Yes House with 3 friends or YesFam members.
To celebrate 8 years of Yes Theory.
This year Seeker's Day will be live for 8 days.
Love you guys.
This is amazing right now
Wow.
I'm now in like a party area. Let's see what we can find.
What's your name?
What's your name you?
I'm Thomas.
I didn't book a hotel. I'm trying to stay with a local in their house.
You want a place?
Yeah, to stay for one night.
One night?
One night, yeah.
Come to my home.
Are you sure?
Give me $2,000.
Cheers, man.
Thank you.
Cheers.
He is searching for a one-person house
You see what I'm saying?
It's like a challenge.
Yeah, exactly.
It's a challenge to sleep in a Lebanese house
What time are you done with your shift here?
1am.
1am?
Do you have a place to stay for me?
Yes.
Where is that?
You know this person?
Yes, he's my little brother.
Really?
Yeah, of course.
Hello
Yes dude
I need a favor
Sure I am at your service
I have a foreigner friend, you know
I want him to sleep over at your house for a night
I can't do it in my house because I have a sister
but you live alone
You see?
So can he sleep over at your place tonight?
Yeah it's okay
Okay, thanks a lot.
See you.
Bye.
He accepted.
Are you serious?
Yes.
But wait, what did you tell him?
This is our friend, Abu Ali Al-Shallab.
Abu Ali Al-Wafo.
Does your friend speak English?
He speaks Arabic.
Only Arabic?
Only Arabic.
And he will stay with you.
Oh, you come with me?
Yes, of course.
You want to go techno?
Whatever, I'll go with you guys anywhere.
Yes.
And look, we are wanted by the police.
What?
No, no, no.
What's up?
I think I just secured a place.
It is currently 9.30pm though and these guys are done with their shift at like 1.30 in the morning.
So, I don't know, I'm either getting kidnapped by these guys or having the best night ever.
Are you guys Lebanese?
I'm trying to find a house or a home to stay at tonight.
So, I'm wondering if anyone is down to host me for tonight.
Do you think I could stay at your place?
It's a bit far.
It's a bit far, sorry.
What about my guy over there?
All good.
That was the least promising response I've ever gotten.
Maybe, maybe the craziest question you ever got in your life.
But imagine if a Swedish person come to Lebanon and he would ask you, can I stay at your house tonight?
I can stay anywhere, on a sofa, on a floor.
We say yes, she says no.
Are you from Lebanon?
Yes.
How down would you be to host me tonight?
Look who I've spotted.
Bro, this is my territory.
This is my territory.
What are you doing here bro?
Trying to find a solution.
This is not working out like we thought it would.
But I had a great time.
I got like, I swear, I got like at least 300 friends today.
At least 300 friends.
So, I'm loving it.
It is a game of numbers.
Having a big old smile.
And what's the percentage that I will find someone tonight?
I'll let the editors decide.
So, editors, what's the percentage right now?
It's half past ten.
We're in Beirut, Lebanon.
What's the percentage?
How are you doing?
Are you feeling good energy?
I've got no option.
Otherwise, I'll sleep on the streets tonight.
Good luck bro.
Two lost boys.
F***ing looking for you.
Looking for a place to stay.
Damn, I'm just walking around and it's like a busy party street.
And we're very close to where the explosion happened.
And this gas station is still completely destroyed.
Seeing that gas station and these rundown buildings in the midst of a busy night life street
just makes me really feel that Lebanon, in so many ways, represents the will to live,
the will to continue with your life despite setbacks,
despite everything around you seeming to work against you.
Hanedi, tell me what's your favorite thing about living in Lebanon?
Really, the people, this feeling that you are never alone,
this sense of community that you have here.
I think this is my favorite thing about this.
Are you from Lebanon?
Yes, we are Lebanese.
Cool, can I ask you a question?
Yeah, sure.
My challenge for tonight is to find someone who would be very spontaneous to say yes
to host me tonight in your house.
Wait, wait, let me check something.
Yeah?
My flatmate is at home.
So it is feasible, it is only 45 minutes away.
Okay, wow, that's so kind.
You're the best people ever here.
Just opening doors.
Okay, his name is Danny.
Okay, okay.
Oh, Danny, this is Staffan.
Marhaba, Danny.
Your new roommate.
Thank you.
I didn't scare you away.
No, no, definitely not.
Right before you said hi, I was going to tell her that you had a friendly face.
Thank you.
I'm going to meet up with your roommate now, and we all have breakfast tomorrow.
Yes, we will.
Let's go!
Is that possible by any chance for you guys to host me?
It's just tonight.
You have to find the right person.
You're not the right person?
Ah, we are traveling tomorrow, man.
Ah, you're traveling tomorrow, okay.
Okay.
Can I be in your vlog?
Let's go.
Alright, let me tell you what I'm doing.
The challenge that I'm doing in Lebanon today is investigating the angriest country in the world.
The idea is for each of us to find a Lebanese person to host us for the first night.
His face is silly.
That's actually amazing.
Yeah.
And it's an amazing idea.
So, do you guys have a floor that I can crash on tonight?
I think I can help you.
Let me ask your friend.
Okay.
That's my friend. He wants to talk to you.
He just wants to know who you are.
Of course.
How are you doing? my name is Ammar
I know it's pretty random
You're talking to a complete stranger on the phone who's asking you to crash on your couch.
If it's okay with you, I would love to join you tonight and crash wherever you have a place for me.
Even if it's the floor.
I don't mind at all.
I need to check with my friend again.
I need to talk to him again.
Yeah, of course.
If you work with me, I'll ask my friend.
Thank you so much, Habib.
It means the world.
Thank you so much.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Okay, I've got some news.
Tell me.
My friends told me that they found a place in Kempinski.
Okay.
And it's Lebanese people?
It's Lebanese people, yes.
You can stay with them.
Are they there right now?
Yes, they're there.
Okay, I'm not going to celebrate too early.
I don't want to get my hopes too high up.
Let's go.
Let's go meet them.
I can also take a taxi.
No, no.
You go with us.
Go with us.
I don't even know their names yet.
Tell me your name
Jawad.
Right Jawad, what about him?
Zein.
Jawad and Zein. I am Ammar.
I hope this works out.
Okay, so I met these lovely two siblings.
And Van has a roommate.
His name is Danny.
So I'm heading to his place now.
Okay, it's currently 1.30 a.m.
And I've had a Red Bull, so...
What's up, bro?
Are we doing this?
You're good?
Yeah, I'm good.
I got a place to stay.
What's the plan?
Okay, so basically, he's got to go on my bike, get you there.
And after, we drink till the morning.
Ammar, Staffan, I hope you're doing all right.
Don't know where you are.
Probably not too far.
We were all here not too long ago.
Okay, so we're in the mountains.
Wait, we're going on this?
Yes.
Where are we going?
To your house?
Yes, to my house.
Bro, what the f*** am I doing?
I'm going to f***ing die on this, bro.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry, mom.
Why?
Because I'm riding without a helmet.
Oh my god, bro.
What the f***?
Am I scared?
Yes.
Yeah.
The life-loving people.
a car with two girls coming out of the roof.
Just like singing their hearts out.
The idea is with the economic crises
all the crisis that's happening
Lebanese people always manage to surprise the world,
no matter how difficult the crisis is
Fun is not an option.
Fun is everywhere.
Yeah.
It's a lifestyle.
If we work, we have fun.
If we study, we have fun.
The Lebanese atmosphere is different from the whole world
Of course, right
Oh wow, this is your place?
Yeah.
Come, bro, Thomas.
Great.
No worries.
Salam.
How are you?
Nice to meet you.
Nice.
Come and sit.
Wow.
Here is your bed.
This?
This is your bed.
Oh my god, okay, great.
Bro, thank you so much.
Nice to meet you.
Am I staying with those guys?
Yeah.
Okay, wow.
But this is your room, right?
Tonight.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
This is my bed for tonight.
Wow, I got a view.
You have a view, but not...
It's so bad, your view.
Thank you for amazing driving.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hello, roommate.
Hey, man.
How are you?
I'm good, man.
All good?
Yeah, thank you.
Nice to meet you.
How are you, man?
Thanks for hosting me.
No, it's all right, man.
All good.
He told me about you.
You're a good guy, so...
All right, I take his word for it.
Let's go.
Oh, we're like on the beach.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a very luxurious place.
Are you gonna stay in?
What's up?
All good?
Hi.
Now we go party.
Yes.
We're going to party.
Bro.
You're freaking crazy, man.
I don't know, bro.
My friend owns the chalet.
He's mad at me so much.
Like, look at the messages.
He said, like, you guys can't stay in the chalet.
What should we do now?
All right, let's go.
You never get an experience like this, staying in a hotel.
He's stopping everywhere.
What's up, bro?
Nice to meet you.
You know everyone in this neighborhood, huh?
Yeah.
He knows everyone?
We're here.
Oh, bro.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you, man.
We're here.
I've got some pringles if you want
or some nuts
I love some nuts.
We're giving you ice cream.
You have to pick one.
Okay, thank you.
So we're watching a movie now as well.
Ice cream, we have chips.
We're having a sleepover.
No pillow fights.
No pillow fights, yeah.
Is he sleeping inside?
Who is sleeping inside?
What's going on?
I feel like I'm in a movie right now.
Although Ammar thought he had a place,
he got caught up in some interpersonal drama,
and now he doesn't have one.
He already cancelled your key
So we're gonna sit down somewhere that is not the room
because right now the owner of the room
has freaked out at the friend group.
And now we have to figure out.
Yeah, we're probably gonna just sleep on the beach here.
Apparently, this club is called UFO.
How are you doing?
Thomas.
I think I've met the mayor here.
You know everyone, bro.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Holy shit.
You can like tip.
Like this?
Don't get your hand stuck.
I think we've arrived.
See you tomorrow.
Holy fuck, bro.
Where am I?
Do you believe in aliens?
I do.
You believe in aliens?
I believe in aliens.
Amazing, man.
What's going on?
WE'RE IN LEBANON
Let's go.
Where am I?
It's 4.30 in the morning.
I needed to be in bed at least 3 hours ago
I ended up in a situation
where the people that were gonna host me
now are looking for a place to stay.
But Alex came through,
so it looks like I'm not homeless after all.
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
Alex is here.
Just four strangers just in my room.
Let's go.
Good night, Danny.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
I'm so extremely grateful
for all the good vibes
that was brought out from this day.
I am going to bed with a full heart
and a great reminder
that a stranger is just a friend you haven't met yet.
Good night.
These people know how to party.
Oh, s***.
It just stopped working.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Alright, what is he gonna do?
One, two, three.
Oh, my God.
You're a freaking crazy man.
See you tomorrow, bro.
Okay, let's go.
Well, this is my humble abode.
I'm gonna try to sleep for a couple of hours
because I'm getting picked up
to go to the beach tomorrow.
Good night.
Good morning
and welcome to day two of the Lebanon adventure.
Okay, I just woke up.
This is the view.
What the f***?
You're awake?
Yes.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Welcome to Lebanon.
I think we're going to the beach.
I'm the only foreigner here.
Wow.
We're in heaven.
Beautiful day.
Beautiful day, yes.
We're in paradise.
Breakfast time.
We just met on the streets.
Yeah, baby.
We've got this guy joining our squad today.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
It's an iconic.
Wow.
Oh, my goodness.
It's iconic.
It's a catfish right here, guys.
Welcome to Lebanon.
After completing our original challenge of staying with strangers
and experiencing something with them,
in an effort to dive deeper and immerse ourselves further
into the culture of this beautiful country,
we spent the next few days meeting locals,
trying some authentic, homemade Lebanese food.
exploring Beirut, and, of course,
It's so good. It's amazing.
I mean, I have a confession.
I've been fortunate to travel to many places,
but I think Lebanon and Syria have the best food in the world.
They do.
People here, you know, they are the happiest, desperate people.
One day you hear on the news there's a clash in the streets,
people are fighting, and the next day they are partying.
During the revolution, one day I was on the street,
and Hadi called me and told me, Mom, come pick me up.
People were on the streets drinking beer, playing cards,
and I was like, where do we live?
Yeah.
Wow.
Coming to the meet-up?
Yes.
Wow, there's...
I mean, since the beginning of Yes Theory.
The community started to meet the Yes Fam.
And Lebanon has been super active.
They've been such a support system for each other
and we wanted to come here and get to understand more how the Yes Fam community has
you know, the role it has played in their lives.
I just wanna say thank you guys for being a part of this community
and showing up for us,
showing up for each other
It's some of the kindest, most hospitable, most life-loving people that we've ever met
The Lebanon was one of the first communities to get activated and
I was so proud to see
Yes Fam rising in the Middle East before any other country
You had many people who got married within our group
We've had people who literally got engaged
It's been an incredible experience.
The sense of community here in Lebanon is incredible.
Like you've always got your family,
You've always got your friends
And that we got the Yes Fam
Where I found my community
To celebrate eight years of Yes Theory and Seekers' day
Staffan Taylor, I challenge you, today in Beirut Lebanon to get your first yes tattoo with me.
Is that a yes?
It's a yes!
As we got to meet more and more people of this country
We couldn't stop ourselves from wondering:
How people in the darkest and most challenging of times
somehow found the strengths and the kindness
to be the most giving
In many ways, that is what I've seen in a lot of countries struggling
That somehow, in the most difficult of times,
our humanity also comes out.
Our deep desire for connection, love and care really does blossom where we're left with so little.
And really, in the moments where we all feel fear or disconnected from the world
Let's remember and take inspiration from the kindness and camaraderie displayed before us.